{
    "questions":[
        {
            
                
                    "question": "What's the name of the city I was born in? ",
                    "correct": "Almaty",
                    "answer2": "Astana",
                    "answer3": "Oakville",
                    "answer4": "Toronto"  
        },
                
           {
                    "question": "What's my birthday?",
                    "correct": "July 27",
                    "answer2": "August 23",
                    "answer3": "March 8",
                    "answer4": "April 3"  
                },
           { 
                    "question": "What's my favorite band?",
                    "correct": "Metallica",
                    "answer2": "ACDC",
                    "answer3": "Guns & Roses",
                    "answer4": "Green Day"    
           },
           { 
                    "question": "What's my favorite color?",
                    "answer4": "Grey",
                    "answer2": "Black",
                    "answer3": "White",
                    "correct": "All of them"    
                },
            {
                    "question": "What's my favorite position to sleep?",
                    "answer3": "On the left side",
                    "answer2": "On the  right side",
                    "correct": "On the back",
                    "answer4": "On the belly"    
                    },
                    { "question": "What's my favorite dish? ",
                        "answer3": "Steak",
                        "answer2": "Sushi",
                        "correct": "Pilaf",
                        "answer4": "Samosa"    
                    },
                    { "question": "Who's my favorite actor? ",
                        "answer3": "Rayan Reinolds",
                        "answer2": "Johny Depp",
                        "correct": "50 cent",
                        "answer4": "Zach Galifianacis"    
                    },
                    { "question": "What's my favorite music genre?",
                        "answer3": "Hip-Hop",
                        "answer2": "Rock",
                        "correct": "Post Rock",
                        "answer4": "EDM"    
                    },
                    { "question": "What's my favorite sport?",
                        "answer3": "Boxing",
                        "answer2": "Soccer",
                        "correct": "Running",
                        "answer4": "Basketball"    
                    },
                    { "question": "What's my favorite copmuter game?",
                        "answer3": "Call of duty",
                        "answer2": "Minecraft",
                        "correct": "Far Cry",
                        "answer4": "GTA"    
                    },
                    {}

           
    ]
}